Guide to the Rice University Assistant to the President papers: Carl MacDowell, 1963-2001 (bulk 1990-1998) UA 084
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: On Campus - General, 1963 – 2000
  - Vice President for External Affairs
    - Vice President for External Affairs/Search, 1989-90 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Vice President for Finance and Administration
    - Administrative/Campus Store, 1991-92 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Associate Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1991-92 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Associate Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1993-94 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Associate Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1995-96 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - (Arthur Andersen) Audit Committee Meeting, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Banner, 1991-93 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1997, 1995-97 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1998, 1996-97 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1981 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Estimated Revenues and Expenditures, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Financial Report, Year Ending June 30, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Financial Report, Year Ending June 30, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Financial Report, Year Ending June 30, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Financial Report, Year Ending June 30, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Process Manual, Fiscal Year Ending 1991 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Budget Director, 1995-97 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Budget Office, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Budget Office, 1995-96 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Budget Office, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Budget Office, 1996-98 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Budget Office/Internally Designated Funds, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Budget Transfers/Sent to NB, 1994-95, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - (Rice) Bus System, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Cable Television Review, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Cashier, 1991-92 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Child Care, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Child Care, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller, 1990-92 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Comptroller, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Controller, 1993-94 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Controller, 1995-96 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Controller, 1996-97 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Deferred Compensation, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Dogs on Campus, 1993, 1995-96 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Discretionary Funds, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Domestic Partner Benefits, 1994-96 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Domestic Partner Benefits, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Plan, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Plan, 1993-94 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Plan, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Plan, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Plan, 1995 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Employer Trip Reduction Plan Committee, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Endowment Spending Rule, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Endowments, 1995-96 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Endowments, Restricted, n. d. (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1991-93 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1995-96 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Excise Tax, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1991-92 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1992-93 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 19996-98 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Facilities and Engineering, 1996-98 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Air Conditioning Schedule, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Campus Upgrade and Modification Reports, 1992-93 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Campus Upgrade and Modification Reports, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Campus Update and Modification Reports, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Campus Upgrade and Modification Reports, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Cogeneration Unit II, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Computer Aided Facilities Management Database Manual, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Energy Conservation, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Stadium Parking Facilities-Report by Walter P. Moore, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Space Inventory, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Space Inventory, 1995-96 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Utilities, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Facilities and Engineering/Utilities, 1994-98 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Club, 1991-92 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Club, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Club, 1995-97 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Food and Housing, 1991-92 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Food and Housing, 1993-94 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Food and Housing, 1995-96 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Food and Housing, 1996-98 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1995-98 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Gift Annuities, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Health Care, 1995-97 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Health Policy, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Human Resources, 1992-93 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Human Resources, 1992-93 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Human Resources, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Human Resources, 1994-95 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Human Resources, 1994-96 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Human Resources, 1995-96 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Human Resources, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Human Resources, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Human Resources, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Human Resources, 1998-99 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Human Resources/Employee Recognition, 1993, 1996-97 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Human Resources/Martin Luther King, 1993-94 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Human Resources/Personnel, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Human Resources/Policy Advisory Committee, 1992-94 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Human Resources/Spousal Employment, 1994-95 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Internal Audit Department, 1991-92 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Internal Audit Department, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Internal Audit Department, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Internal Audit Department, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Internal Audit Department, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Internal Audit Department, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - IRS Audit, 1995-96 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - IRS Audit, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Investment Policy, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Investment Sub-Committee, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - KTRU, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - KTRU, 1993-94 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Liability Insurance, 1987, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Liability Insurance, 1990, 1995-96 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Long-Range Planning, 1995-96 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Mailroom, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Medical Insurance, 1995-96 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Milford House Auction, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Pace Concerts/Eagles, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Pace Concerts/Pink Floyd, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Parking, 1991-92 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Parking, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Parking, 1993-94 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Parking, 1995-96 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Parking, 1995-97 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Parking Letters, 1992 (Folder 1) (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Parking Letters, 1992 (Folder 2) (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - (University) Planning, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - (Campus) Police, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - (Campus) Police, 1995 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - (Campus) Police, 1995-96 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - (Campus) Police, 1997-98 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - President's/Provost's Reserves, 1995-96 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - President's/Provost's Reserves, 1997-99 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Printing and Reproduction, 1994-96 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Promotion and Tenure, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Promotion and Tenure, 1996-97 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Promotion and Tenure, 1996-97 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Purchasing and Receiving, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - (Central) Purchasing Review, 1992, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing Study, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Relocation Expenses, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Research Accounting, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Retirement/Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Retirement, 1998-99 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Retirement/Certified Financial Planners, 1998-2000 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Retirement/Faculty Demographics, 1998 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Retirement/Faculty Retirement Incentive Opportunities, 1998 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Retirement/Faculty Retirement Issues, 1994-98 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Retirement/Faculty Retirement Issues, 1998-99 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Retirement/Medical Insurance for Retirees, 1998-99 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Retirement/Pensions, 1995-96 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Retirement/Princeton Retirement Survey, 1996-97 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Retirement/Program, 1987-89 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Retirement/Program, 1994-96 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Retirement/Program, 1997-98 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Retirement/(Rice's) Retirement Plan Offer, 1996-98 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Retirement/TIAA-CREF, 1997 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Rice Trust, Inc., 1995-96 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Rice Trust, Inc., 1997 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Rice Trust, Inc., 1998 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Safety/Chemical Hygiene Plan (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Salaries, 1993-94 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Salaries, 1996-97 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - (Campus) Security, 1993 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - (Campus) Security, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - (Campus) Security, 1994-96 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Staff Advisory Committee, 1995-98 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Staff Council, 1992, 1996 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Staff Training and Development Committee, 1993 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - TIAA/CREF/Business-Higher Education Forum, 1999 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Telecommunications, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Temporary Employment, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Texas Water Commission/Water Samples, 1993-94 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Travel Advances, 1995 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer, 1986-1990,1992-93 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer, 1990, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer, 1995-96 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer, 1997-98 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1989-92 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1990-93 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1992-93 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1993-94 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1995-96 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1998 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Budget Office/Currie Plan, 1989 (Folder 1) (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Budget Office/Currie Plan, 1988-89 (Folder 2) (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Child Support/Report and Appendices, 1994 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Vice President for Graduate Studies, Research and Information Technology
    - Administrative Computing, 1991-92 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Computing, 1993, 1995 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Apple Service Center, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Computer Security, 1994-95 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Computing, 1986, 1989, 1994 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1994-95 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1996 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Fondren Library, 1991-92 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Fondren Library, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Fondren Library, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Fondren Library, 1994-96 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Fondren Library, 1996-97 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Fondren Library/Owl Sculpture by Bob Guelich, 1994-95 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Fondren Library/Planning Committee, 1993-95 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Fondren Library/Planning Committee (Humanities), 1994-95 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Fondren Library/Planning Committee, 1996-97 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Applications, 1993-95 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Applications, 1996 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Student Affairs, 1992 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Student Association, 1991-92 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Student Association, 1992-93 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Student Association, 1993-95 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Student Association, 1995-96 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Studies, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Studies, 1991-92 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Studies, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Studies, 1994 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Intellectual Property, 1995-96 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - IBM Transition, 1994 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Internet II, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Office of Computing Information Services (OCIS), 1990-92 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Office of Computing Information Services, 1990, 1992-93 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Office of Computing Information Services, 1993-95 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Office of Computing Information Services, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Office of Networking and Computing Systems, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1987-88, 1991-92 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1990-92 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1990-93 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1993-94 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1994-95 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1994-96 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Office of Sponsored Research/Indirect Cost Recovery, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Office of Sponsored Research/Institutional Biosafety Committee, 1994 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Research Accounting, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Research Accounting, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Sesquinet, 1995-96 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Technology Transfer, 1988-89, 1991-93 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Technology Transfer, 1994-98 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Undergraduates in Research, 1994-96 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Vice President for Graduate Studies, Research and Information Technology, 1992-94 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Vice President for Graduate Studies, Research and Information Technology, 1993-95 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Vice President for Graduate Studies, Research and Information Technology (Gorry, Tony), 1992-96 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Vice President for Graduate Studies, Research and Information Technology, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Vice President for Research and Information Technology, 1991-93 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Vice Provost/Librarian Search, 1995-96 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Vice Provost for Research and Graduate Studies, 1994-96 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Vice Provost for Research and Graduate Studies/Search, 1995-96 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Vice President for Research and Graduate Studies
    - Basic Research, 1997-98, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1995-97 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Fondren Library, 1996-98 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Fondren Library, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Fondren Library/Board of Advisors, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Fondren Library/Planning, 1997-98 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Fondren Library/Texshare, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Student Association, 1995-98 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Studies, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Studies, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Indirect Cost 1997 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Intellectual Property, 1996-98 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Intellectual Property/Advisory Board, n. d. (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Office of Sponsored Research, 1997-98 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Research Misconduct, 1995, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Royalties, 1996-97 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Sesquinet, 1996-98 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Technology Transfer, 1997-98 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Vice President for Information Technology, 1997-98 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Vice Provost for Research and Graduate Studies, 1997-98 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Vice Provost/University Librarian, 1997-98 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - (The) Washington Advisory Group (WAG), 1997-98 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Y2K Millennium Bug, 1997-98 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Y2K Millennium Bug, 1996-99 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs
    - Academic Advising, 1991-92 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Academic Advising, 1990-94 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Academic Advising, 1993-95 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Academic Advising, 1994-95 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Academic Advising, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Academic Advising, 1997 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - (Campus) Alcohol Policy, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Black Student Association, 1993-94 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Career Services, 1991-92 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Career Services, 1993 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Career Services, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Career Services, 1993-95 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Career Services, 1995-96 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Career Services, 1996-97 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - (Disciplinary) Cases (see staff instructions) (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - (Disciplinary) Cases (see staff instructions) (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - (Disciplinary) Cases (see staff instructions) (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - (Disciplinary) Cases (see staff instructions) (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - College Based Courses, 1992-94 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - College Based Courses, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - College Based Courses, 1995-97 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - College Course Lecturer, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - College Course Lecturer, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - College Masters, 1991-93 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - College Masters, 1994-95 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - College Masters, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - College Masters, 1997-99 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Colleges, Baker, 1992-93 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Colleges, Brown, 1993-97 (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Colleges, Brown-Richardson Co-Ed Conversion, 1977, 1980, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Colleges, Hanszen, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Colleges, Jones, 1993-94 (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Colleges, Lovett, 1991-92 (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - Colleges, Richardson, 1989, 1992-94 (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Colleges, Richardson, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Colleges, Wiess, 1994-96 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Colleges, Wiess, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Colleges/Residential, 1989-92 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Colleges/Residential, 1992-93 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Colleges/Residential, 1994-96 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Colleges/Residential, 1997-98 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Copyright Information, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - (Rice) Crew Club (Rowing), 1989 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - (Rice) Cycling Team, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Dean of Students, 1993-95 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Dean of Students, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Disabled Student Services, 1997-98 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Disabled Student Services, Alviar, Hector,1994, 1996-97 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Exchange Program/Cambridge, 1994-95 (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Exchange Program/Kyushu University, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - Exchange Program/Trinity University, 1996-97, 1999-2000 (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Foreign Academic Advising/International Services, 1994-96 (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Academic Advising/International Services, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Student Advising/International Services, 1996-98 (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - Forensic Society, 1994-96 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Forensic Society, 1995-96 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Graduate House, 1992-93 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Graduate House, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Graduate House, 1995-97 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Graduate House, 1998 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Habitat for Humanity, 1995-96 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Health Professions Advising (Pre-Med), 1990-91 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Hillel, 1991, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Honor Council, 1995-96 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Honor Council, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Honor Roll History – President's Office, 1995-96 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Honor System, 1993-96 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Institute of European Studies (IES), 1994 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Intramurals, 1994-95, 1997 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - John Hancock Health Insurance, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Judicial Affairs, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - (Ad Hoc Committee of the) Judicial Process (Box 141, Folder 18)
    - Judiciary, 1995 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary, 1997 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Language Houses, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Leadership Rice, 1995-96 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Rice, 1997-98 (Box 142, Folder 6)